diplomatie.be 2003-06-07

# Privacy

## Privacy Policy

Privacy policy

Collected data

The name and e-mail address you fill in to be registered on the mailing list are processed by the Federal Public Service Foreign Affairs, Foreign Trade and Development Cooperation (hereafter FPS), located at Rue des Carmelites 1, 1000 Brussels. The FPS complies with the law of 8 December 1992 on the protection of privacy with respect to the processing of personal data and with the law of 11 December 1998 transposing Directive 95/46/EC of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data.

You yourself provide us with personal identifiable data such as your name, address, mobile phone number, gender, date and place of birth, telephone and fax numbers, identity card number and current e-mail address. Cookies are not used to collect personally identifiable data except for your language of preference when you visit the website.

Cookies are small information files that are automatically saved on your computer's hard drive to facilitate access to the site and make navigating easier, faster and more efficient, and to personalise this site in line with your personal preferences, e.g. your preferred language. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that produced it. The configuration of most browsers allows you to either accept or reject cookies as well as to indicate whenever a cookie is used. Rejecting the use of cookies can lessen your optimal navigation of the site. For further information, please consult your browser's help function. 

Use of your personal data

We neither make use of your personal data, nor pass them on to third parties.
